Guide to the Gitel P. Steed Papers 1907-1980
University of Chicago Library
- Series III: Kasandra, 1950
  - Subseries 8: Caste and Kinship
    - Koli-Patels, pregnancy ceremony financing, interview (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Koli-Patels, James Silverberg research notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Koli-Patels, James Silverberg research notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Koli-Patels, James Silverberg research notes, going to a fair, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Koli-Patels, James Silverberg research notes, relations with outsiders, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Koli-Patels, James Silverberg research notes, relations with Koli-Pagis, dissertation notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Koli-Patels, James Silverberg research notes, relations with Vaghela-Rajputs and other Rajputs (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Koli-Patels, James Silverberg research notes, relations with other village castes (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Koli-Patels, James Silverberg research notes, relations with other Koli-Patels (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Koli-Pagi, census, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Koli-Thakardas (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Bawas (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Bharwad (Herdsman) (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Rat (Barber) (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Kumbhars (Potters) (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Rawal (Donkey Carrier) (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 9: Economics
    - Index to general notes, extracts (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Intercaste economic relations, hereditary service, land tenure, Rajput social categories, charts, undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - General notes, extracts (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - James Silverberg general notes, extracts, mother's-brother's-daughter marriage char. (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Land tenure, disputes, agriculture, trade, census, correspondence, tracts, newspaper clipping (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Land tenure, disputes, agriculture, trade, census, correspondence, tracts, newspaper clippin. (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Land tenure, disputes, agriculture, trade, census, correspondence, tracts, newspaper clipping (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Land Utilization Survey, milk production, questionnaire forms, undated (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Vaghela-Rajputs, economic relations (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Vaghela-Rajputs, genealogy, J. P. Peile data, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Jhala-Rajputs, Talukdars, genealogy, land tenure history, J. P. Peile data, Gazatteer extracts, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Reforms and changes, general notes, extracts (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Bombay province government organizational charts, interview, "Some Aspects of Entrepreneurship in Western India," manuscripts, note by James Silverberg, 1950, 1978, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Kumaruppa, J. C., "A Survey of Matar Taluka," manuscript, notes, 931, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Patel, M. D., "An Analytical Survey of Forty Years' Breeding Work in the Improvement of Kankrei Cattle," manuscript excerpts, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 10: Land Tenure
    - Land Economics, labor relations, charts, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Land Economics, landholdings, land types, charts, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Land Economics, survey data, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Vaghela-Rajput, "Caste, Clan, and Territory," historical chart, genealogy, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Land tenure, charts, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Thooti, Vaishnavas of Gujerat, maps, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Khata-vati (Village) Settlement Register, Nos. 400-498, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Khata-vati (Village) Settlement Register, August 26, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Khata-vati (Village) Settlement Register, August 26, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 11: Land Utilization Survey
    - Completed forms, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Completed forms, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Completed forms, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Completed forms, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Banya, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Patels, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Patels, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Vagharis, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Dhobi, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Rawal, undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Harijan-dhed cultivators, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Harijans, undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Totals, Book I, undated (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Totals, Book II, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Totals, Book III, undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Land tenure, Village Record of Rights, Informant 3 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Land Economics, crops, tabulations, chart, 1949-1950 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Desai, N. K., "Agricultural Resources and Class Structure in Taluqdari village in Ahmedabad District (North Gujerat) 1949-1950," manuscript, correspondence, 1959, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 12: The Structure of Family and Child Life
    - Preliminary models, reading notes, questionnaires, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary models, reading notes, questionnaires, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Life cycle (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - "The Structure of Child Behavior," outline, notes, 1950, 1959. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Index Two, Child's Community (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Banya children on the death of a young relative (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Child study, index (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Child study, index (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Child study, death of a Banya infant (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Informant 58, notes, genealogy (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Informant 58, notes, genealogy (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Informant 58, notes on art drawings. (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Informant 58, Rorschach, TAT, H-H, Draw-a-man, genealogy, index (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Singer, Milton, "Basic and Modal Personality," manuscript, 1953. (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Misc. general note extracts (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 13: Religion
    - Indexes, classificatory, calendar, temple priest data (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Indexes, classificatory, calendar, temple priest data (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Index, chronological (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Index, classified, life history, general (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Religion and ritual, index, sacred geography (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Festivals and rituals, ritual calendar, general note extracts (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Lecture 14 notes, chapter notes, general note extracts, 1950-1953, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Lecture 14 notes, chapter notes, general note extracts, 1950-1953, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Lecture 14 notes, chapter notes, general note extracts, 1950-1953, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Festivals (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Bhajans, bhakti (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Worship practices, pitras, surdhans, Divali (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Sorcery, ritual curing practices (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Sorcery, goddess possession, ghosts, dreams (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Personal religion (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Religion and land tenure (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Temple priests, interviews (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Religious personnel (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Religious principles, scriptures, texts, literature (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Bhajans, members of the mandali (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Ritual calender, extracts (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Ritual calender, extracts (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Word lists (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Note and lecture extracts (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Notes (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Notes (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 14: Field Notebooks, Gitel P. Steed
    - Diary, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Diary, 1951 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Language lesson (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - London, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - I, method of selecting villages, November 28, 1949-January 21, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - II, projective methods, December 11, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - III, Rorschachs, January (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - IV, Rorschachs (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - V, method of selecting villages 2, January 20-28 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - VI, January 28-February 3 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - VIII, February 4-11 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - IX, February 11-16 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - X, February 17-22 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - XI, February 23-26 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - XII, February 27-March 5 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - XIII, March 5-10 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - XIV, March 10-15 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - XV, March 15-April 1 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - XVI, April 1-4 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - XVII, April 4-9 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - XVIII, April 9-15 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - XVIII, April 9-15 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - XIX, April 16-21 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - XX, April 22-May 8 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - XXI, May 8-12 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - XXII, May 12-16 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - XXIII, Deoli, June-July (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - XXIV, July 17-19, August 15 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - XXV, Informant 1, July 15-July 26 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - XXVI, Informant 8, July 19-August 15 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - XXVII, July 20-26 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - XXVIII, Informant 7 and others, July 20-October 6 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - XXIX, Informants 16 and 26, July 21-November 12 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - XXX, Informant 10, July 19-29 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - XXXI, Banyas and others, July 23-11 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - XXXI, additional notes, July 22, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - XXXII, Rorschachs, July 23-August 19 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - XXXIII, Informant 3, July 26-28 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - XXXIV, July 26-August 2 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - XXXV, Informant 2, July 27-August 5 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - XXXVI, Informant 10, July 30-August 25 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - XXXVII, Informant 1, July 31-August 15 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - XXXVIII, August 4-14 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - XXXIX, Kumbhar (Potter), July 1950-January 4, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - XL, Informant 3, August 7-18 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - XLI, boys, Color Association Test, Child Development Test, August 5, 1950-January 2, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - XLII, Informant 2, August 8-24 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - XLIII, Informants 41, 58, Banya children, August 9-December 3 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - XLIV, August 14-22 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - XLV, Informant 1, August 15-December 8 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - XLVI, Informant 8, August 17-October 30 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - XLVII, Rorshachs, August 22-28 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - XLVIII, Informant 3 and family, Informant 4, August 22-December 1 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - XLIX, Jain-Banyas, August 22-December 11 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - XLIX, Informant 21, August 22-December 8 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - L, August 22-31 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - LI, Informant 2, August 22-December 6 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - LII, August 31-September 6 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - LIII, Rorshachs, September 12-November 19 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - LIV, October 21-30 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - LV, Color Association Tests, October 22-December 31 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - LVI, Informant 18, others, October 23-28 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - LVII, Harijans, October 23-November 2 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - LVIII, Color Association tests, October 28-December 24 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - LIX, Women, October 29-December 27 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - LX, Rorschach, TAT, October (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - LXI, October 30 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - LXII, October 30-November 8 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - LXIII, Darbar women, November 7-30 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - LXIV, November 8-29 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - LXV, November 19-December 16 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - LXV, November 19-December 16 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - LXVI, Rorschachs, November 1-December 2 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - LXVII, Informant 9 and family, November 21-December 12 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - LXVIII, Life history interviews, November 24, 1950-January 2, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - LXVIII, Life history interviews, November 24, 1950-January 2, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - LXIX, tests, November 26, 1950-January 5, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - LXX, TAT, November 29, 1950-January 1, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - LXX, index, undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - LXXI, TAT, November 31-December 22 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - LXXII, Darbar women, December 1-6 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - LXXII, Informants 4 and 7, index, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - LXXIII, Darbar women, December 6-14 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - LXXIV, Informant 11, dream, December 1 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - LXXIV, December 8-23 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - LXXIV, January 12, 1951 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - LXXV, tests, December 17, 1950-January 3, 1951 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 15: Field Notebooks, James Silverberg
    - Diary (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Diary (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Diary, 1951 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Linguistics-Phonetics, January 30 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - I, Rorschach, January 25-February 5 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - I, Rorschach, January 25-February 5 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Unnumbered, January 16-February 6 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - II, February 8-16 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - III, February 16-24 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - IV, Mukund Shastri Gujerati notes, February 22-March 4 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - V, March 4-8 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - VI, March 9-18 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - VII, March 8-22 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - VIII, March 22-28 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - IX, March 29-April 7 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - X, April 7-16 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - XI, April 6-19 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - XII, April 19-21 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - XIII, April 21-23 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - XIV, June 30-July 3 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - XV, July 3-5 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - XVI, July 5-8 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - XVII, July 8-9 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - XVIII, July 10-11 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - XIX, July 10-13 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - XX, July 13-16 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - XXI, July 16-21 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - XXII, July 21-24 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - XXIII, life histories, July 23-November 14 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - XXIV, Informants 5 and 25, July 24-29 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - XXV, July 25-27 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - XXVI, Rorshachs, October 21-29 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - XXVII, Informant 15, October 24-December 2 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - XXVIII, Informant 31, funeral, October 26-December 13 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - XXIX, Informant 1, October 28-November 21 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - XXX, Rorshachs, October 29-November 22 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - XXXI, Informant 14, October 28-December 30 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - XXXII, Rorshachs, November 1-8 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - XXXIII, Informant 19, November 4-December 7 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - XXXIV, Informant 20, November 9-14 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - XXXV, November 11-25 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - XXXVI, Informant 13, November 11-December 5 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - XXXVII, Rorschachs, November 12-19 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - XXXVIII, Informant 23, November 15-29 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - XXXIX, November 16-December 30 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - XL, Rorschachs, Color Association Test, Nov. 20-Dec. 27 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - XLI, Informant 6, November 22-December 10 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - XLIV, Informant 12, November 27-December 3 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - XLV, Informant 20, November 29 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - XLVIII, Color Association Test, December 23-27 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 16: Notebooks by others
    - Masher, Bhavati, I, January 28-March 14 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Masher, II, January 31-March 22 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Masher, III, June 7-August 7 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Masher, IV, January 2-March 30 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Massey, Cecil B., I, January 3-July 3 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Massey, II, March 3-April 25 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Massey, III, January 31-February 18 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Mehta, Kantilal, April 10-December 22. (2) (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Mehta, Kantilal, April 10-December 22. (2) (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Dosajh, N.L., March (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Informant 3, undated (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Steed, Robert, Project accounts, Jan. 28, 1950-Jan. 22, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 17: Drawings
    - List of informants. (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Watercolors and drawings, tabulations (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Watercolors and drawings, tabulations (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Watercolors and drawings, tabulations (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Village art statistics, tables. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Watercolors, Informants 3-36 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Watercolors, Informants 37-39 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Watercolors, Informants 40-56 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Watercolors, Informants 58 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Watercolors, Informants 58 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Watercolors, Informants 58 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Watercolors, Informants 59-71 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Watercolors, Informants 72-84 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Watercolors, Informants 81 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Watercolors, Informants 85-88 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Watercolors, Informants 89-102 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Watercolors, Informants 104-169 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Watercolors, unidentified (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Drawings, interview, Informant 40 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Drawings, interview, Informant 41 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Drawings, Informants 58 and 88 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Drawings, interviews (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Drawings, interviews (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Drawings, interviews (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Drawings, interviews (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Drawings, interviews (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Drawings, unidentified (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Cinema leaflet (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 18: Interviews, 1970-1971
    - Brahmin schoolmaster (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Rajputs, marriage practices, visit to Thakur Saheb, kinship (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Vaghela Rajput, Informant 1 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Vaghela Rajput, Informant 2 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Vaghela Rajput, unnumbered informant (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Vaghela Rajput, women (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Vaghela Rajput, group interview (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Vaghela Rajput, school for Darbars (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Jhala Rajput, Informant 3's death (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Jhala Rajput, unnumbered informant (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Jhala Rajput, kinship, social control (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Solunki Rajput (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Chauhan Rajput (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Jain Banya (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Koli-Pagi (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Bharwad (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Shenma (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Dheds (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Misc. castes. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Misc. castes, college student list (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Religion, Ramdev Pir, legend, performance, correspondence, 1971, undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Delhi, Surindra Singh Soreri on Kerala (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Ahmedabad, A. A. Khartri, sociology (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Ahmedabad, Mr. Lassiter, Rural Electrification Project (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Field notebook (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Field notebook, loose notes (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Interview, November 29, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Interviews and notebooks, note added by James Silverberg, 1970, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Drawings, "Twilight of the Overlord System," manuscript draft, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Series IV: Nawabpur Files, 1951
  This series contains eleven subseries and includes similar material to those listed above for Kasandra. Nawabpur was a predominantly Muslim village in Uttar Pradesh where the researchers moved for their second year in India. Steed left halfway through their stay in Nawabpur due to illness, and James Silverberg took over the direction of the project during her absence. Steed's general notebooks were continued, in series, by other researchers after she left the field. There are additionally a series of notes taken by Grace Langley, an American graduate student who joined the project as an assistant this second year.
  - Subseries 1: Informant Life Histories
    - List of informants, list of informant watercolors and drawings, incomplete (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Informant 1, personal narration (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Unnumbered informant, personal narration (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 2: Psychodiagnostic Tests
    - Rorschachs (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Horn-Hellersberg (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Horn-Hellersberg (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Horn-Hellersberg (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Color Association (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Color Association (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Color Association, Hofstra University, 1951, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 3: General Notes, Gitel P. Steed
    - Word list, crops and cultivating implements. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Index outlines. (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Visiting Nawabpur with McKim Marriott, January 18-31. (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - February 13-21 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - February 13-21 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 4: General Notes, Chamars and Bhangis, Grace Langley
    - August 13-September 22 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - August 13-September 22 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - August 13-September 22 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - August 13-September 22 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - September 13 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - September 13 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - September 24-October 8 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - September 24-October 8 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - September 24-October 8 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 5: Census Data
    - Household register (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Household register (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Household register (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Caste and kinship, genealogies (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Kunba data, genealogies (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Maps, genealogies, survey notes (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Medical survey (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 6: Topical Files
    - Land tenure, Census tabulations (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Land tenure, Court cases (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Land tenure, Collectorate records, translation of khatauni, 1937 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Land tenure, Collectorate records, translation of khatauni, 1937 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Land tenure, Collectorate records, translation of khatauni, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Land tenure, Collectorate records, translation of khasra for 1937 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Land tenure, Collectorate records, translation of khasra for 1937 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Caste and personality traits, Questionnaires, drafts, UNESCO study in group tensions, repsondent list (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Caste and personality traits, Questionnaires, completed (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Caste and personality traits, Questionnaires, completed (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Caste and personality traits, Grace Langley notes (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Land Utilization Survey, Tabulations on land tenure, food and fodder production, ratings summary (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Land Utilization Survey, Questionnaire form, blanks (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Land Utilization Survey, Muslim Rajputs (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Land Utilization Survey, Muslim Rajputs (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Land Utilization Survey, Muslim Rajputs (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Land Utilization Survey, Muslim Rajputs (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Land Utilization Survey, Kachis (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Land Utilization Survey, Jatavs (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Land Utilization Survey, Dhimars, Barbers (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Land Utilization Survey, Dhobis (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Land Utilization Survey, Sweepers (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Land Utilization Survey, Misc. Hindus (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Religion, Wedding and funeral rituals (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Religion, Holi, Phuldo organization (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Religion, Mosher, Arthur T., "The Economic Effect of Hindu Religious and Social Traditions on Agricultural Production by Christians in North India," dissertation chapter, table of contents, 1946 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Religion, Islam, Marshall Hodgson lectures, "Hindu-Muslim Tensions in Aligarh," "UNESCO Tension Research," manuscripts, 1951, undated (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Court cases, crime, 1948-1951 (Box 60, Folder 10)